‎搞什么
What the fuck?
‎开什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
‎该死
Motherfucker.
‎“犯罪历史”
"Criminal past"?
‎圣安东尼奥当地一名记者 ‎昨晚发布了这篇报道…
A local reporter in San Antonio posted the story last night--
‎赛斯 直接讲 ‎“犯罪历史”是怎么回事
Seth, skip to the "criminal past" part.
‎1996年 在16岁的时候
When he was 16 years old, so this is in 1996,
‎亚伦非法将一名 ‎叫作马里卢斯圣地亚哥的
Aaron illegally transported a undocumented child
‎无身份儿童 带入了美国境内
named Mariluz Santiago across the United States border.
‎-我们都不知情吗 ‎-是的 在审查时没有发现这件事
-We didn't know about this? -No, it didn't show up in the vet.
‎叫所有人去椭圆形办公室 马上
Get everybody in the Oval. Now.
第三季   第七集
指定
幸存者
‎联邦调查局认为事件已结束
The FBI considers the matter closed.
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
精校
发行
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
‎没什么好惊讶的
Oh, you can't be surprised by that.
‎他们的运营预算里 ‎有个分账项目就是为蝴蝶结设的
Their operational budget has a line item for bows.
‎他们喜欢用那玩意来打包结案
They like to tie up their cases with them.
‎我听懂了 汉娜 只是并不觉得有趣
I got it, Hannah. I just didn't find it amusing.
‎情况比他们想的要复杂得多
It's a lot more complicated than they think.
‎-还有没查清的线索 ‎-对
-There are loose ends. - Right.
‎“夺回我们的国家”这个组织
So, our racist friends in Reclaim Our Nation,
‎不得不说 这个名字挺适合 ‎做单一种族州的州名
which, I have to say, very catchy name for an ethnostate,
‎这个组织里的种族主义伙伴们 ‎非法贩运
they were trafficking in biological compounds
‎我们在剑桥和坦帕发现的 ‎DIY实验室合成的生物化合物
synthesized at the DIY labs we found in Cambridge and Tampa.
‎-那些片段是从哪里来的 ‎-什么片段
-So, where did the pieces come from? -The pieces?
‎合成用的组件 一段段小基因片段 ‎被他们编辑起来
The components. The little genetic bits they CRISPR together
‎成为邪恶的自制病毒
into their diabolical custom bugs.
‎它们来自一家叫作“遗传”的公司
They come from a company called Genetical.
‎问题是 片段不是实验室采购的
The point is, the bits weren't ordered by the lab.
‎而是波士顿北部一家啤酒厂订购的
They were ordered by another business, a brewery north of Boston.
‎怎么 你觉得这家啤酒厂 ‎是交易中间人
And you think, what, that this brewery is some sort of clearinghouse?
‎是他们把片段送去实验室的
That they send the bits to the lab?
‎这值得进一步调查
It merits further investigation.
‎好 去查清楚
Okay, check it out.
‎如果超出了国内恐怖主义的范畴
If we're moving beyond domestic terrorists,
‎我可以找个朋友问问
I can speak to a friend who may have some insight
‎他也许知道这次行动的幕后黑手是谁
into who's ringleading this operation.
‎你在想什么
What were you thinking?
‎先生 当时我还小 ‎我照我阿姨的话…
Sir, I was a teenager. I did what my aunt asked--
‎我不是说当时 而是现在
I'm not talking about then, I'm talking about now.
‎你应该明白 为什么不说出来
You know better. Why keep this to yourself?
‎-现在是关键时期… ‎-他告诉过我
-It's the height of-- -He told me.
‎-我告诉他不要告诉别人 ‎-你告诉他什么
-And I told him to keep it to himself. -You told him what?
‎请不要责备她 ‎这是我的错 我做的决定
Please, don't blame her. This is on me. I made the call.
‎这种事情轮不到你做决定
You don't get to make the call about a subject like that.
‎我们也有传递矛盾信息的问题
We also have a problem with mixed messages.
‎总统刚刚驱逐了一个 ‎非法进入这个国家的家庭
The president just deported a family for entering the country illegally,
‎你就成了打开边境的海报男孩
and you've become the poster boy for open borders.
‎总统先生 我应该辞去竞选身份
Mr. President, I should resign from the ticket.
‎-等演讲结束后再说 ‎-什么演讲
-We'll see how the speech goes. -Speech?
‎我们宣布你将在今晚九点 ‎在白宫东厅发表演讲
We've advised that you'll make an address at 9:00 p.m. from the East Room.
‎我会抢占西海岸本地新闻的资源
It'll preempt local news on the West Coast.
‎-所有有线电视都会直播 ‎-这是为了什么
-All the cables will carry it live. -This is meant for what?
‎为了给你个机会
To give you the opportunity
‎对全国人民说句 ‎有说服力的“怪我不好”
to deliver a convincing mea culpa to the country.
‎所以你现在这种顽固无悔的态度
So this unrepentant thing you got going,
‎最好尽快换成悔悟的情绪
you better smooth it over with contrition ASAP.
‎我建议你们去干活 就这样
I suggest you get to work. That's all.
‎艾米丽
Emily.
‎是 先生
Yes, sir.
‎我需要你写两份声明
I need you to write two statements.
‎一份为亚伦继续竞选准备 ‎另一份则为他退选准备
One if Aaron stays on the ticket, one if he goes.
‎与此同时 写一份你自己的辞职信
While you're at it, draft your own resignation letter.
‎之后我会告诉你是否用得上 去吧
I'll let you know if I need it later. Go.
‎我反应过度了吗
Am I overreacting here?
‎不 完全没有
No, not at all.
‎非受迫性失误
Unforced errors.
‎该死的非受迫性失误
Goddamn unforced errors.
‎林怎么样了
How's Lynn?
‎好些了 先生
Better, sir.
‎-她还在医院吗 ‎-是
-She still in the hospital? -Yes.
‎但昨晚她恢复意识了
But she regained consciousness last night,
‎看来最糟的时候已经过去了
so looks like she's through the worst of it.
‎好 有新消息再告诉我
Okay, good. Keep me posted.
‎我会的 谢谢您 先生
I will. Thank you, sir.
‎我该说什么“抱歉 我把一个 ‎为社会做贡献的人带来了这个国家
What should I say? "I'm sorry for bringing a contributing member of society
‎这个国家满是天生就具有国籍和特权
into our country that's filled with natural-born, entitled assholes
‎却不知感恩的混蛋”
who take their citizenship and privilege for granted."
‎-我不会开头就这么说 ‎-该死
-Well, I wouldn't lead with that. -Shit.
‎听好 如果是我 ‎我不认为你做错了任何事
Look, if it's me, I don't think you did anything wrong.
‎我觉得你不该为此羞愧
I don't think you have anything to be ashamed of.
‎但是现在的情况呢 ‎这是教科书般的楔子问题
But this? This is the definition of a wedge issue.
‎-天啊 ‎-你要小心
-Jesus. -But you gotta take care
‎别太强硬 以免疏远自由主义阵营
not to be so hard-line as to alienate the liberal base.
‎但也要足够强硬
But then, you gotta be just hard-line enough
‎说服无党派人士 ‎你在移民问题上没有过分仁慈
to convince Independents you're not overly lenient on immigration.
‎-你找我 ‎-不是你 是她
-You need me? -No, her.
‎你可以的
You got this.
‎-总统先生 ‎-你找我
-Mr. President. -You wanted to see me?
‎萨莎 请进 快请坐
Sasha, please, come and sit down.
‎国会警察告诉了我 ‎在女洗手间发生的意外
The Capitol Police told me about the incident at the women's washroom.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎你怎么没来跟我说
Why didn't you come talk to me?
‎为什么要说 ‎这种事经常发生 没人在乎
Why? This kind of thing happens all the time. No one cares.
‎莫斯在乎 他的代理人们 ‎正在电视上闪电作战
Moss does. His surrogates are in the middle of a TV blitz
‎想要拿这件事做文章 化为己用
trying to spin the incident in his favor.
‎-请别用那个词 ‎-哪个词
-Please stop using that word. -What word?
‎“意外” 那不是意外 ‎那就是我的生活
"Incident." It wasn't an incident. This is my life.
‎这更说明我们应该反击
It's all the more reason why we need to push back.
‎“我们”是谁
Who's "we"?
‎是你
You.
‎绝对不要
Absolutely not.
‎我完全理解这有多么艰难
I can only imagine how difficult this is.
‎你不是刚做了个演讲 ‎歌颂隐私的重要吗
Didn't you just give a speech extolling the virtues of privacy?
‎你想说什么大家都有隐私权
What was your point? That everyone has a right to privacy
‎-除非破坏隐私对你有好处 ‎-萨莎 这事和我无关
-except when it's convenient for you? -Sasha, this isn't about me.
‎没错 和我有关 我的回答是不
That's right, it's about me. And my answer is no.
‎-还有别的事吗 ‎-没有
-Is there anything else? -No.
‎很抱歉 非常感谢
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
‎我知道我是在 ‎从局外人的角度看待这件事
I know I'm looking at this from the outside in,
‎但我们得做点什么 想办法回应
but we need to do something. Figure out a way to respond.
‎是 先生
Yes, sir.
‎凯洛格将军
General Kellogg.
‎我有一个潜在国家安全问题 ‎需要提请您注意
I have a potential national security issue I need to bring to your attention.
‎好
All right.
‎两架北美防空 ‎联合司令部的F-22战斗机
Two NORAD F-22s intercepted
‎在我们的防空识别区拦截了几架 ‎俄罗斯图-95熊式轰炸机
a couple of Russian Tu-95 Bear bombers in our Air Defense Identification Zone.
‎具体在什么位置
And where exactly is that?
‎科迪亚克岛往南一些 在阿拉斯加湾
Little bit south of Kodiak Island in the Gulf of Alaska.
‎如果那些图-95轰炸机 ‎继续按当前航线飞行
If the Tu-95s continue on their current course,
‎这完全是假设
and that is a big if,
‎那它们将在三小时内飞越西雅图
they'll overfly Seattle in just three hours.
‎通常他们会在惹急我们之前返航
And normally, they turn around before they give us too much heartburn,
‎但我们会在战情室密切监视
but we'll monitor this from the Sit Room.
‎我和你一起走
I'm coming with you.
‎我想看看 现在我们能不能
I wanna see if there's anything we can do
‎用拜杜法案的介入权条款做点什么
with that march-in clause from the Bayh-Dole Act.
‎太好了 你有什么想法
Great. What do you have in mind?
‎还没有联邦政府机构监管过
No federal agency ever exercised its oversight
‎这些大型混蛋制药公司 ‎剥夺他们的专利
in stripping these Big Pharma bastards of their patents.
‎我们不应像用手术刀一样 ‎小心翼翼地用这则条款
We shouldn't be using this clause as a scalpel.
‎而应该像用棍棒一样
We should be using it as a cudgel.
‎我可以联系 ‎我在国立卫生研究院的熟人
Well, I can get in touch with my contact at NIH.
‎看看有什么其他 ‎可以收回的执照 给你…
See what other licenses might be reclaimable, get you--
‎我想专门查一家公司 叫弗莱格坎德
Yeah, I'd prefer to look at a specific company. FlagKind.
‎找到他们的弱点 打击他们
Find out where they're vulnerable, then let's go after them.
‎只查弗莱格坎德是有什么原因吗
Any reason why we're only focusing on FlagKind?
‎因为我叫你去查 ‎查到了什么就来告诉我
Because I asked you to. Let me know what you come up with.
‎这里的制造部门看上去不太繁荣
Manufacturing sector doesn't look to be thriving here.
‎我不关心他们的利润率
It's not their profit margin I'm interested in.
‎我一直不太喜欢国内啤酒
Never been a fan of domestic brews.
‎除非是精酿啤酒 说到这个 我…
Unless we're talking craft beers, in which case, you can count me in...
‎她还是这副开心的面容 好吧
Unrelenting delight, she is.
朝圣啤酒酿造公司
‎我们这是什么处境
So, where are we?
‎亚伦为什么不跟我们说实话 ‎我们本可以处理这个事情
Why wasn't Aaron honest with us? We could've managed the story.
‎是啊 但无论 ‎你做什么决定 都要尽快
True. But whatever you decide, you gotta do it fast.
‎现在的关键是果断 ‎特别是在你的对手
Decisiveness is key here. Especially when your opponents
‎说你一事无成、优柔寡断的时候
are characterizing you as ineffectual and irresolute.
‎“一事无成、优柔寡断” ‎我理解莫斯竞选团队为什么这么说
"Ineffectual and irresolute." I get that from the Moss campaign.
‎但我不理解为什么媒体不写 ‎在我任总统期间
I don't get why the press isn't writing that during my presidency,
‎我成功解决了一次人质危机 ‎处理恐怖分子和自然灾害
I successfully navigated a hostage crisis, dealt with terrorists, natural disasters.
‎甚至还有国会
Hell, even the Congress.
‎更不用说在一次史无前例的灾难后
Not to mention, rebuilt the United States government
‎重塑美国政府 他们还想要我怎样
after an unprecedented disaster. What the hell do they want from me?
‎能请你从一幢着火的建筑里 ‎救出一个婴儿吗
Could you rescue a baby from a burning building, please?
‎总统先生 我们有麻烦了
Mr. President. We have a problem.
‎其中一架图-95 ‎在十分钟前脱离队伍
One of the Tu-95s split off ten minutes ago,
‎-回头飞往俄罗斯 ‎-其中一架
-headed back towards Russia. -One of them?
‎这是从未有过的 先生 ‎飞行都需两两组队
It's unprecedented, sir. They do these runs in pairs.
‎你评估一下是什么情况
What's your assessment?
‎F-22战斗机 ‎紧跟离队的熊式轰炸机
The F-22s stayed on the tail of our rogue Bear.
‎他们报告说挡风玻璃昏暗 已经结冰
They reported the windshield is dark and iced up.
‎我们扇动机翼和俄罗斯机组人员沟通
We waved our wings to communicate with the Russian crew,
‎但没有得到回应 先生
but we got no response, sir.
‎一架飞机无法袭击 这说不通
They're not attacking us with one plane. That doesn't make sense.
‎你觉得机组人员出事了
You think something's happened to the crew?
‎我们只能猜想是这样 先生
That's our best guess, sir.
‎我们猜想他们的补充氧气失效 ‎他们晕过去了
We're assuming their supplemental oxygen failed and they blacked out.
‎最好的情况 就是机组人员 ‎失去行动能力 未能醒来
So, best case scenario, crew is incapacitated, not waking up.
‎给我说说图-95上的武器系统
Tell me about the weapons system on the Tu-95.
‎如果核武器处于活跃状态 ‎飞机击中西雅图的话
If the nukes are live and it hits Seattle,
‎很可能导致二十五万人死亡
we're looking at a high estimation of 250,000 dead.
‎先生 飞机距离美国大陆 ‎只有一小时行程
And, sir, the plane is an hour away from US mainland.
‎如果想击落它 要立即在海面上进行
If we want to shoot it down, we need to do it over water, and now.
‎我们不能击落俄罗斯飞机
We're not shooting down a Russian plane,
‎哪怕机组人员已经死亡 ‎我们也要先和莫斯科沟通
even if the crew's dead, until we talk to Moscow.
‎用热线 告诉他们 ‎我要和他们的总统通话
Use the hotline. Tell them I need to speak to their president.
‎是 先生
Yes, sir.
‎该死
Shit.
‎这再一次证明 一个意外当选 ‎后知后觉的总统 没有做好准备
This is another example of an unprepared, oblivious, accidental president
‎他只能听从条款的指挥 ‎而不会运用条款
who's letting the terms dictate him, instead of him dictating the terms.
‎科尼利厄斯莫斯有足够的经验 ‎可以领导美国…
Cornelius Moss has the necessary experience to lead the American...
‎-嘿 你的演讲写完了吗 ‎-我正在忙一件事
Hey, have you finished your speech? I'm in the middle of something.
‎我也在忙一件事 ‎这件事就是总统选举
I'm in the middle of something, too. It's called a presidential campaign.
‎我们马上就要失败了 都是拜你所赐
Which we're currently losing, no small thanks to you.
‎我也是国家安全顾问 ‎现在这个工作更重要
I'm also the national security advisor, and right now, that takes precedence.
‎-嘿 ‎-嘿 如果你要用办公室 我可以走
Hey. Hey, if you need your office, I can go.
‎不 不用 我很期待 ‎去哈奇法案监狱探望你
No, stay. I'm looking forward to visiting you in Hatch Act jail.
‎别翻我的第一个抽屉就行
Just don't snoop in my top drawer.
‎嘿 不 等一下
Oh, hey, no, hold on there.
‎这个指尖陀螺的数量也太不合理了
This is an unreasonable amount of fidget spinners.
‎赛斯 我…这东西根本都没人在玩了
Seth, I... These aren't even a thing anymore.
‎-你很有问题 ‎-我有很多问题
-You have a problem. -I have a lot of problems.
‎你知道战情室出什么事了吗
Um, do you know what's happening in the Sit Room?
‎-好像出现了骚乱 ‎-不知道
-Seems like there's commotion afoot. -No idea.
‎我被关在这里 ‎努力找一种合理的措词
I've been cooped up in here trying to find an eloquent way
‎可能要结束我朋友的政治生涯 ‎以及我自己的
to potentially end my friend's political career, as well as my own.
‎-他不会开除你的 ‎-你确定因为换作我 我会
-He's not gonna fire you. -You sure? Because I would fire me.
‎怎么了
What?
‎莫斯和他的喽啰 ‎在电视新闻上大肆报道萨莎的事
Moss and his goons, they're already all over cable news with this Sasha thing.
‎想把她描述成自由祸害
They're making it seem like she's some sort of liberal scourge.
‎他们还用她转换性别前的名字指代她
They're deadnaming her, using her pretransition name.
‎我直到今天才知道她的曾用名
I didn't even know what that was until today.
‎我觉得这不是什么问题
I don't see the problem.
‎让她上脱口秀 接受报纸采访
Get her on some talk shows, do a newspaper interview,
‎把她贴上《名利场》的封面 ‎让那群混蛋明白他们就是些跳梁小丑
slap her on the cover of Vanity Fair, put those assholes in their place.
‎她是个内向的人 ‎不想处在众人的注视下
She's a private person. She doesn't wanna be in the limelight.
‎我知道 我也知道她不想
I know that, and I know she doesn't.
‎我说这话可能有点刻薄 ‎但也许她应该走出来
This might sound a little bitchy, but maybe she should get out of it.
‎-这样不太公平 ‎-你说得对 这不公平
-That's not exactly fair. -You're right, it isn't fair.
‎但同样不公平的是 ‎上百万人在无声地忍受痛苦
But what also isn't fair is that there are millions of people suffering in silence
‎因为他们不是总统的小姨子 ‎没有特权
because they don't have the privilege of being the president's sister-in-law.
‎我很难去同情一个
It's hard to sympathize with someone
‎能够发出有影响力的声音 ‎却选择不发声的人
whose voice could make an impact and just chooses not to use it.
‎-说到特权… ‎-抱歉
-Speaking of privilege... -Sorry.
‎好吧 我该怎么让她去利用特权
Okay. So how do I get her to use it?
‎我不知道 你最擅长说服的艺术
I don't know. You are so skilled in the art of persuasion.
‎说服她
Persuade.
‎我可以继续工作了吗
Can I get back to work now?
‎可以 只是…
Yeah. Only just, uh...
‎-别 天啊 ‎-我不得不 上瘾了
-Don't. God. -I have to. It's an addiction.
‎2018说了 要把玩具要回去
2018 called, wants its toy back.
‎马斯嘿 我迅速审查了一下 ‎弗莱格坎德的产线
Mars? Hey. I did a quick vet on FlagKind's product line.
‎然后呢
And?
‎都是内部生产、自主研发的
They were all generated in-house with proprietary R&D,
‎没有联邦资助
no federal funding.
‎所以都不受制于政府的介入权
So, none of them would be subject to march-in rights.
‎要不换一家公司
Maybe another company?
‎不要换公司 就要这家公司
Not another company, this company.
‎如果你找不到我要的东西 ‎我就自己来
If you can't get me what I need, I'll take care of this myself.
速度和服务 ‎
这就是朝圣者的方式
送货
‎有什么事吗 女士
Can I help you, miss?
‎我想找你们经理
I was hoping to speak to a manager.
‎我们这儿严格来说没有经理
Uh, we don't have a manager, strictly speaking.
‎经营方式没那么正式
More of an informal operation.
‎我是酿酒师 所以应该资历比较高
I'm the brewmaster, though, so I suppose I got seniority.
‎这是你的酒厂
So this is your place?
‎对 这里是家族经营 好几代人了
Mine enough. Been in the family for generations.
‎你们有没有从一家叫“遗传”的公司
Have you guys purchased specialized materials
‎买过专业材料
from a company called Genetical?
‎你们是从什么地方来的
Where are you from?
‎卫生和公众服务部
Department of Health and Human Services.
‎你们为什么订购过一批
Why would you have ordered a shipment
‎天花病毒的基因片段
containing genetic components of the smallpox virus?
‎天花不是已经从地球上消失了吗
Smallpox? Didn't they wipe that off the face of the earth?
‎我是在遗传公司订过货 ‎但没有你们说的那种危险品
Look, I've ordered from Genetical before, but nothing hazardous like you say.
‎合成啤酒花 组合用的片段
Synthetic hops, pieces to put 'em together.
‎-真好 转基因啤酒 ‎-对 我们正在研发
-Brilliant. A GMO beer? -Yeah, we're working on it.
‎这是行业的未来
Future of the industry.
‎实用、有生态意识、省水 ‎能为重要作物让出空间
Sensible, eco-conscious, saves water, makes room for more essential crops.
‎对 我祖父听到一定很生气 ‎但这样口味也更好
Yes. My grandfather would hate to hear it, but it tastes better, too.
‎我已经不再从遗传公司进货了
I stopped buying from Genetical.
‎客户服务很糟 货运也一团糟
Customer service is terrible. Shipping's a mess.
‎他们要是出错 我也不会感到意外
I'm not surprised they made a mistake.
‎感谢你抽空和我们聊 抱歉打扰了
Thanks for your time. Sorry to bother you.
‎不打扰
It's no bother at all.
‎嘿 你知道可以找谁 ‎来帮忙推销你们的啤酒吗
Hey, you know who you could get to endorse your beer when it comes out?
‎格隆
Gronk.
‎-格隆考夫斯基 ‎-是 好主意
-Gronkowski. -Oh, yeah, great idea.
‎对吧他很乐意帮人招揽生意 ‎爱国者队加油
Right? I mean, he'll shill for anyone.  Go Pats.
‎爱国者队加油
Go Pats.
‎在这边北方长大的人 ‎不支持爱国者队是么
Guy grew up north of here, he doesn't ride for the Patriots? Right.
‎你说的爱国者队 ‎是橄榄球队员 是吧
And your Patriots are American footballers, yeah?
‎格隆是在本地 ‎很受欢迎的冠军之类的
And this Gronk is some kind of beloved regional champion?
‎对 如果你在这里长大 ‎这就像你的宗教一样
Oh, yeah. And if you grew up here, it's your religion.
‎他说遗传公司记录混乱的问题
That thing he said about Genetical's record-keeping being a mess,
‎-对你来说可信吗 ‎-可疑
-that sound credible to you? -Doubtful.
‎干我们这行的多少有些强迫症
Most of us in this racket have a touch of the OCD.
‎我在遗传公司的朋友一直吹毛求疵
My mate in Genetical's chronically anal.
‎刚刚那话有点吉尔伯特 ‎与沙利文的幽默意味 是不是
That last bit sounded almost Gilbert and Sullivan, didn't it?
‎去问你朋友吧 等今天结束
Just check with your mate. And when the day's done,
‎我会回到这调查一下
I'll come back here and give it a shakedown.
‎你喜欢这样 是不是
-You love this, don't you? -Hmm?
‎追捕的刺激 逼近猎物之类的
Thrill of the chase, the charge of the hunt, all that?
‎我想是的
Yeah, I guess I do.
‎俄罗斯国防部长 ‎接通了热线 戈洛文将军
The Russian minister of defense is on the hotline. General Golovin.
‎-戈洛文将军 ‎-总统先生
-General Golovin. -Mr. President.
‎几分钟内 你们的一架轰炸机 ‎就会进入我们领空
Within minutes, one of your bombers is going to enter our airspace.
‎如果你们不干预 ‎我们将必须将其击落
If you don't intervene, we will have to shoot it down.
‎目前的状况在我们的掌控之中
We have the situation under control.
‎从我们的利益角度来看并非如此
It doesn't look like that from our vantage point.
‎你们在干什么
What are you doing?
‎-我无权讨论这件事 ‎-你最好开始讨论
-I am not authorized to discuss that. -You better start.
‎我们没时间了
We're running out of time.
‎你们远程解除 ‎飞机上装载的核武器了吗
Have you remotely disarmed the nukes onboard?
‎和美国一样
Like the United States, the Russian Federation
‎俄罗斯联邦既不承认 ‎也不否认其飞机或潜艇上
neither confirms or denies the presence of nuclear weapons
‎有核武器
on its planes or submarines.
‎你最好转告你们总统
You better tell your president
‎你们有十分钟的时间处理轰炸机 ‎不然我们会采取措施
you've got ten minutes to deal with this bomber, or we will.
‎决定权在您 总统先生 ‎因为那是你们的领空
It is your decision, Mr. President, as it is your airspace.
‎按你们自己的意愿行动 ‎不过要小心谨慎
Do what you will, but tread very carefully.
‎该死
Son of a bitch.
‎-他们对这个情况感到尴尬 ‎-那是自然
-They're embarrassed by the situation. -They should be.
‎还有一个选项我们没有讨论过
There's an alternative we haven't discussed yet.
‎你到现在才说
You're waiting till now to tell me that?
‎这很反常规
It's quite outside the box.
‎但我们要让网络司令部一起来讨论
But we need to bring Cyber Command into the conversation.
‎-这个状况他们可以帮忙 ‎-叫他们来 马斯在哪
-They could help us out here. -Bring 'em in. Where the hell is Mars?
美国食品药品管理局局长
G德特维尔 ‎2012年-2016年
H里克特 2016年至今
‎哈珀先生 局长准备好了 ‎他说抱歉让你久等了
Mr. Harper, the commissioner's ready. He apologizes for the wait.
‎不要紧 里克特局长
No harm, no foul. Commissioner Richter.
‎耽搁我的事情确实紧急 ‎但我担心你觉得被冒犯了
I'd say the hold-up was urgent, but I worry you'd take offense.
‎-什么事情 ‎-刚打完一个电话
-How do you mean? -Just wrapped a call
‎是关于爬行类幼崽和沙门氏菌的 ‎并不是公开的工作职责中的一部分
on baby reptiles and salmonella. Not in the public job description.
‎现在已经没什么工作 ‎是属于公开工作职责的了
Seems that nothing is these days.
‎感谢您抽出空接见
Thanks for taking the time.
‎如果是关于我的接任工作的话
If this has something to do with my handover,
‎我已经列好了一些可能合适的候选人
I've compiled a list of possible candidates.
‎主要是前顾问 ‎以及一些公正的政策…
You know, mostly some former advisors, some equitable policy--
‎和你的继任者无关
This has nothing to do with your succession.
‎-那有什么我可以做的吗 ‎-弗莱格坎德
-Then what can I do for you? -FlagKind.
‎他们怎么了
What about them?
‎他们在等待批准的新药 ‎有传言说药物正在进行临床试验
Their new drug up for approval? Rumor has it that it's in clinical trials.
‎没错 是的
Correct, it is.
‎情况会如乔丹弗莱格所愿吗
How's that looking for Jordan Flagg?
‎我想食品药品管理局会继续按传统
I'm assuming the FDA's gonna continue its tradition
‎让他的产品走快速通道吧
of granting his products fast-track treatment?
‎哈珀先生 我…
Mr. Harper, I...
‎你知道的 我不能讨论 ‎进行中的审查进展
You know this. I can't discuss an ongoing review process.
‎-这样会… ‎-有违职业道德
-I mean, it would be-- -Unethical?
‎和制造一款 ‎令超过两百万人上瘾的药物
As unethical as manufacturing a drug that addicts more than two million people,
‎再创造另一种抵制药瘾的产品一样 ‎没有职业道德吗
and then creating another to counteract that addiction?
‎这个对话会给我们双方 ‎都带来很多麻烦
This discussion could land each of us in a good bit of trouble.
‎我觉得为了我们彼此的利益 ‎最好到此为止
I think it's in both of our best interests that we end it here.
‎出于好意
As a matter of courtesy,
‎我会忘记所有谈话内容
I'll forget we spoke more than two words between us.
‎谢谢您 局长
Thank you, Commissioner.
‎你在闲逛吗
Are you loitering?
‎我更愿意称之为“迷人地偷闲”
I would prefer that we called it "attractively idling."
‎我等着和总统聊没聊完的事
I'm waiting to finish a conversation with the president.
‎我们被战情室的状况打断了
We were interrupted by a situation in the Situation Room.
‎-有内部消息吗 ‎-很遗憾 没有
-Any intel? -I'm afraid not.
‎-你见到艾米丽了吗 ‎-见到了 她在我办公室 备受煎熬
Have you seen Emily? -Yeah, she's in my office, suffering. -Hmm.
‎在我看来 柯克曼先生 ‎是个软弱而又一厢情愿的勤杂工
It seems to me that Mr. Kirkman is a weak and willing factotum
‎他为我们国家极致的自由影响者服务
to the most extreme liberal influencers in our country,
‎萧先生扮演着墨西哥入侵者的赞助人
with Mr. Shore acting as sponsor to Mexican invaders
‎而柯克曼的前小舅子 ‎则在白宫推进激进的跨性别议题
and Mr. Kirkman's former brother-in-law pushing a radical transgender agenda,
‎这话真拗口
say that five times fast, in the White House.
‎科尼利厄斯莫斯没有忘记
Now, Cornelius Moss has not forgotten
‎平凡、努力、传统的美国人…
the normal, hard-working, traditional-minded Americans...
‎贱人、婊子、畜生、垃圾
Son of a bitch, motherfucker, piece of shit, cunt.
‎抱歉
Sorry.
‎我也会这么说
I wouldn't change a word.
‎黛安 你都不联系我了
Dianne. Who never calls me anymore.
‎你现在在私营部门了 道夫
You're in the private sector now, Dov.
‎我们没有可以聊的话题了
We have nothing to share.
‎不 我还有很多东西 ‎可以跟你分享 亲爱的
Oh, no, no, no, I still have so much to share with you, motek.
‎-别激动 宝贝 ‎-他一旦来了兴致
-Down, boy. -Well, once he gets up,
‎就很难再平静下来 但你懂的
it is so very difficult to put him down again. But you know this.
‎我有个问题 你宝贵的专业知识
I have a question, one that could benefit from your
‎-也许能帮忙 ‎-你说
-invaluable expertise. -Of course.
‎过去参与生化武器项目的科学家
Scientists involved in chemical and biological weapons programs
‎有谁还在活跃
back in the day, who's still in the game?
‎你可以去问英国人的
You could have gone to the British for answers,
‎或者加拿大人、澳大利亚人 ‎为什么问我
the Canadians, the Australians. Why me?
‎以色列在二十世纪九十年代 ‎帮助过南非的核项目
It's an open secret that Israel helped South Africa
‎这已是公开的秘密
with their nuclear program in the '90s.
‎你们的政府可能也帮助过
Less of an open secret that your government
‎他们的生物武器研究 ‎这个秘密就没那么众所周知了
may have also helped them with their bioweapons research.
‎具体说 是他们的 ‎种族目标生物武器研究
Specifically, their racially-targeted bioweapons research.
‎是 你说的是海岸线计划
Yes, you're referring to their Project Coast.
‎我们当然知道 但那不是我们的事务
We knew about it, of course, but it wasn't our affair.
‎摩萨德肯定会密切关注主要事项
Surely Mossad kept tabs on the principals.
‎再问一次 还有谁在活跃中
So, again, who's still in the game?
‎我们失去线索的 ‎唯一一个海岸线计划成员
The only one from Project Coast that we lost track of
‎是一个名叫伍特蒙伯格的男人
was a man named Wouter Momberg.
‎要我说 他是最病态的一个 ‎他也许已经死了
Sickest of the lot if you ask me. He could be dead,
‎也许伪装死亡 也许失踪了
could have faked his death, could be in the wind.
‎-你有最近的记录吗 ‎-我可以帮你找
-Do you have a most recent trace? -I can get it for you.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎在过去
You know, in the old days,
‎为了这种信息 ‎你可是会跨坐在我身上的
you would have straddled me for information like this.
‎让我们看看后续如何吧 宝贝
Well, let's just see how this plays out, Liebchen.
‎抱歉 我本该告诉你的
I'm sorry, I should've told you.
‎该接受你道歉的人不是我
I'm not the one you owe the apology to.
‎但你也确实对不起我 ‎声明写得怎么样了
Although, you know, sort of, I am. How are those statements coming?
‎对不起
- -Sorry.
‎喂 出什么事了
Hello, what's wrong?
‎你能不能 强迫她吃
Well, can you, I don't know, make her eat?
‎我明白 好吧 ‎我也不知道 告诉她我尽快
I understand. Okay. I don't know exactly, but tell her as soon as I can.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎好 这话我只说一次
Okay, I'm only gonna say this once,
‎如果让我发誓 ‎我可能会否认说过这话
and if I'm asked about it under oath, I will probably deny,
‎有时候…
but sometimes...
‎家人更重要
family takes priority.
‎听起来眼下就适用
And it sounds like this is one of those times.
‎正处于第三次离婚 ‎最后阶段的女人如是说
Take it from the lady who's in the home stretch of her third divorce.
‎这些怎么办我一定要写完
What about these? I have to finish them.
‎我可以帮你完成
Yeah, I'll finish those up.
‎怎么了我也得找点事做
What? I need something to do.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎-还是不要这样了 ‎-真抱歉
Oh. Yeah, let's not do that. -So sorry. -Mmm-hmm.
‎总统先生 这位是施耐德上将
Mr. President, Admiral Schneider.
‎上将 我知道你可能有解决方案
Admiral, I understand you may have a solution for us here.
‎2016年 我们修复了一架 ‎坠毁在叙利亚的
In 2016, we recovered a Russian-made MiG-29KR
‎俄罗斯制米格-29KR
that went down in Syria.
‎通过对其进行逆向分析研究
Did some reverse engineering
‎掌握了侵入敌军战斗机 ‎自动驾驶程序的方法
and learned how we might hack the automatic pilots of enemy fighters.
‎在您下令后 我们可以开始侵入
On your command, we can initiate the hack,
‎尝试将轰炸机路线重新导向太平洋
try to redirect the bomber's course back over the Pacific.
‎-能成功吗 ‎-我们不知道 先生
- Will it work? -We don't know, sir.
‎从没有在实战中测试过
It's never been tested in the field.
‎没有别人知道我们有这项技术
No one else knows that we have this technology?
‎我想是的 因为我是 ‎第一次知道它的存在
I'm assuming that because it's the first I've ever heard of it.
‎如果现在使用 ‎我们就失去了这个优势
If we use it now, we give away that game.
‎你怎么看
What do you think?
‎这项技术就是为眼下这种状况准备的
The tech is designed to work in a situation like this.
‎如果没成功 没人会知道它
If it doesn't work, no one's the wiser.
‎如果成功了 泄露秘密也要比
If it works, revealing the secret's a whole lot better
‎让核弹在美国领土上爆炸要好得多
than having nuclear bombs setting off on American soil.
‎我同意 准备开始吧
I agree. Set it up.
‎艾米丽 嘿 你知道亚伦在哪吗
Emily. Hey, do you know where Aaron is, by any chance?
‎他不在他办公室
-He's not in his office. - Uh...
‎显然战情室有什么 ‎需要全员到场的紧急事件…
Apparently there's some all-hands-on-deck in the Situation Room, so...
‎嘿 虽然有点尴尬
Hey. This is awkward.
‎我听说亚伦把马里卢斯圣地亚哥的 ‎秘密告诉了你 是真的吗
Uh, I heard Aaron confided in you about Mariluz Santiago. Is that true?
‎你知道他为什么告诉了你 ‎却没告诉我吗
Do you know why he would tell you and not me?
‎不 我不知道 ‎我们一起参与竞选工作 所以…
Um, no, I don't know. You know, we were working on the campaign together, so...
‎你应该问他 我该走了 抱歉
You should ask him about it. I gotta go. I'm sorry.
‎当蒂
Dontae!
‎新闻发言人先生
Mr. Press Secretary.
‎呀 对 你怎么样了伙计没事吧
Oh, shit, right. How you doing, man? You okay?
‎没事 多谢关心
I am. Thanks for asking.
‎-说说别的事吧 ‎-对 抱歉
-Let's talk about something else. -Yeah, sorry.
‎你还记得你帮伊莎贝尔做的视频吗
So, you know how you helped Isabel with those video testimonials?
‎说服制药公司 ‎不要再做贪婪的混蛋的那些视频
Persuade the drug company to stop being a rapacious asshole?
‎她跟你说了
She told you about that?
‎我想问你能不能帮我做类似的东西
I'm wondering if you can help me with something similar.
‎用来说服萨莎
Something to persuade Sasha.
‎不是说她是个贪婪的混蛋
Not that she's a rapacious asshole,
‎但我想说服她参与某些事
but something to persuade her to, you know, engage.
‎比如呢跨性别快剪视频
Like, with what? A transgender supercut?
‎如果你要这么说的话…
Well, if you're gonna put it that way...
‎我有更好的主意
I got a better idea.
‎-嗨 妈妈 ‎-嗨 宝贝
-Hi, Mom. -Hi, sweetheart.
‎她看起来很愉快
She seems cheery.
‎刚给她吃了止痛药 ‎应该能再撑四个小时
Just gave her the pain meds. She should be good for another four hours.
‎-我猜她没吃东西 ‎-没有 她说她不饿
-I'm guessing she didn't eat? -No, she said she wasn't hungry.
‎她经常这么说
Yeah, she says that a lot.
‎当病人不再进食时
When patients stop eating,
‎特别是病情处于你母亲这个阶段的话 ‎这往往是个信号
especially at your mother's stage, it's usually a signal.
‎这是让我们知道 他们准备好要走了
It's to let us know they're ready to go.
‎她最后要做的事的计划都安排好了
All the plans are in place for her last steps.
‎等你准备好了就告诉我
Just let me know when you're ready.
‎早上见
See you in the morning.
‎马斯 你知道这里是怎么回事吗
Mars. Do you know what is going on around here?
‎为什么在竞选危机当中 ‎所有人都消失了
Why has everyone disappeared in the midst of a campaign crisis?
‎媒体都快把我们杀了 ‎我却找不到总统
We're getting killed in the press, and I can't get the president.
‎找不到副总统候选人 再过几个小时
I can't get my VP candidate, who's supposed to be saving his own bacon
‎他就要在全国电视前 ‎挽救自己捅的篓子 而你则擅离职守
on national TV in a couple of hours. You've been totally AWOL.
‎战情室到底怎么了
What the fuck is happening in the Situation Room?
‎我不知道 罗琳 我会尽快搞清楚
I don't know, Lorraine. I'll do what I can to find out.
‎我讨厌追着男人跑
I hate chasing men.
‎很高兴你能来
- -Nice of you to join us.
‎上将 怎么样了
Admiral, where are we at?
‎我们准备好了 等您命令
We're ready to go on your command.
‎可以开始 联系联邦航空局 ‎清空附近领空
You're a go. Contact the FAA, clear the immediate airspace.
‎如果飞机不调头 我们就
If the plane doesn't turn, we'll take it down
‎-在尤马蒂拉国家森林上空击落它 ‎-是 先生
-over the Umatilla National Forest. -Yes, sir.
‎如果上面有核武器呢
If there are nukes onboard?
‎我们祈祷不会爆炸
We pray they don't detonate.
‎侵入系统启动了 先生
The hack is initiated, sir.
自动飞行驾驶模式覆盖 ‎传输进度
‎入侵代码已上传
- Malware uploaded.
‎拜托 混蛋 调头啊
Come on, you son of a bitch. Turn.
‎它调头了
She's turning!
‎完美完成 总统先生
Nicely done, Mr. President.
‎完美完成 亚伦 干得好 将军
Nicely done, Aaron. Great job, General. Great job.
‎上将 非常感谢你 ‎将军 机上还有多少燃料
Admiral, thank you very, very much. General, how much fuel is onboard?
‎差不多七个小时吧
Seven hours worth, give or take.
‎按这个航线 ‎她应该会落入中途岛以北
At this trajectory, she should go down just north of Midway Island,
‎远离任何人口中心 先生
far away from any population centers, sir.
‎太棒了 做得好 各位 非常感谢
Fantastic. Great work, everyone. Thank you very much.
‎-里面都解决了 ‎-圆满解决
-Everything peachy in there? -Peachy keen.
‎好 你的草稿能拿给我看了吗
All right. So, do you have a draft that I can look at?
‎提词器的工作人员肯定也想要
I'm sure the teleprompter people would like to see it, too.
‎我们整天都在忙着处理一个危机
-We've been dealing with a crisis all day. - Hmm.
‎电视讲话要推迟了
We'll have to postpone the remarks.
‎不
Uh, no. Whoa.
‎我们一定要做
Whoa. The fuck we are.
‎你们忙着在战情室玩陆军棋的时候
While you've been in the Sit Room playing Stratego,
‎莫斯的军犬已经席卷了新闻
Moss' attack dogs have been all over the news,
‎把你比作偷渡总司令
making you out to be coyote-in-chief.
‎如果现在不扭转报道 ‎就这样了 你就完了
If we don't seize the story back right now, that's it. You're done.
‎听到她的话了
You heard the lady.
‎好 把脸刮干净 有点大人样
Okay. So, shave that pretty face and put on your big-girl panties.
‎生死关头了
It's do-or-die time.
‎谢谢你能来 我知道总统会感谢你的
Thanks for coming. I know the president appreciates it.
‎我来只是因为你邀请了我
I'm only here because you asked me.
‎不是为了总统 ‎更不是为了他的那头小新闻猎犬
Not for the president, and definitely not for that little press hound of his.
‎赛斯是个好人
Seth's a good guy.
‎他太让人精疲力尽了 ‎像个吸食可卡因的施莱纳会员
Ugh, he's so exhausting. -Like a Shriner on cocaine. -
‎别担心 我挺愿意成为施莱纳会员的
Oops. No worries. I'd love to be a Shriner.
‎他们的小汽车是少妇杀手
Their tiny cars are chick magnets.
‎我们开始吧
Let's get started.
‎我看到今晚有几个新面孔 ‎这是个安全的空间
I see we have a few new faces tonight. This is a safe space.
‎欢迎探讨 但不欢迎评价
Discussion is welcome, judgment is not.
‎谁想第一个说
Who wants to begin?
‎我第一次了解跨性别
My first introduction to transness was those
‎是在《毛利波维奇》节目的 ‎女扮男装环节
disgusting female impersonator segments on Maury Povich.
‎我从那里了解到这个概念
So, it was, like, an introduction to the concept,
‎但没有了解其中人性的一面
but not the humanity of it.
‎所以我们很多跨性别人士
So many of us as trans people,
‎很多日子里 我们都在想 ‎“今天我要如何活下去”
so much of our day is like, "How do I stay alive today?"
‎这很灰暗
And it's, like, that's dark.
‎我有朋友被开除 ‎丢掉工作、无家可回
I've had friends who have been fired, lost their jobs, are homeless,
‎只是因为他们上班时表示 ‎“我就是这样”
because they simply just came to work and said, "I'm me."
‎有些日子里很容易保持骄傲
Some days, it's easy to be full of pride,
‎但有时候 你不得不填你的出生姓名
and some days you have to fill out something with your birth name
‎因为还没有改 你看着它
'cause it's not changed yet, and you see it,
‎这就能毁掉一切 你再也不能呼吸
and it destroys everything. You can't breathe anymore.
‎根据我去的地方以及当时的时间
Depending on where I go or what time of the day it is,
‎我要使用不同洗手间 ‎现在这很让人烦心
using different washrooms is so nerve-racking now.
‎因为过去 如果有性别 ‎我可以直接用女洗手间
'Cause before, if they were gendered, I would just use the women's washroom.
‎这完全是另一个层级的恐惧
It's a whole other level of, like, fear.
‎我受到的待遇要好一些
There's a privilege that I'm getting.
‎这个群体的上一代人令我受益良多
I benefited a lot from the previous generation in this community.
‎我们都花了生命中太多时间 ‎假装自己是别人
We all spent so much of our life pretending to be somebody else.
‎这就说明我们在回避自己
And that means that, like, we're hiding from ourselves,
‎回避爱我们的人
and from the people that love us,
‎归根结底 如果要隐藏真正的自己
and at the end of the day, like, when we have to hide who we are,
‎我们和爱我们的人都会受伤
both us and the people that love us lose.
‎你呢你有什么要和我们分享的吗
How about you? Is there anything you'd like to share with us?
‎-我只想倾听 这样可以吗 ‎-当然
-I'd just like to listen, if that's okay? -Of course.
‎现在我觉得我处在一个很棒的空间
Now, I find that I'm in this really great space
‎在这里我可以为自己的跨性别而骄傲
where I'm so proud of my transness
‎我为自己的公开状态和受关注度 ‎感到骄傲
and I'm so proud of my outness and my visibility.
‎我就是跨性别者的样子 ‎我们每个人都是
I am what trans looks like. Every single one of us is.
‎所以我们应该为自己骄傲
And that's why we should just be proud for ourselves,
‎这样别人就能看到我们的尊严
so others can see our pride.
‎吃吧
Eat.
‎我会的 我只是不饿
I would, I'm just not hungry.
‎我知道 但我不管 ‎这是汤 拜托 把汤喝了
I know and I just don't care. It's soup. Please eat the soup.
‎真是今时不同往日
How the tables have turned.
‎妈妈 我知道你可能已经准备好了
Mom, I know you might be ready,
‎但我还没有
but I'm not. Not yet.
‎没关系 亲爱的
That's okay, pop-tart.
‎我反正还有 ‎很多集《同妻俱乐部》可以看
I still have a bunch of Grace and Frankies to watch, anyway.
‎有食品药品管理局的电话
Call incoming from the FDA.
‎喂 是的
Hello. Yes.
‎我有兴趣 是的
I would be interested, yes.
‎现在我马上来
Right now? I'm on my way.
‎我要离开一下 让他们把车开来
I'm going off campus. Have them bring the car around.
‎演讲怎么样了
How's the speech coming?
‎都是些虚假的愤怒
It's all this fake outrage.
‎新闻真正应该报道的 ‎是我今天处理的事
What the real story should be about is what I did today.
‎无人知晓的工作 保护这个国家
The work no one knows about, protecting this country.
‎好吧 忘掉他们的期待
Okay, forget about what they're expecting,
‎忘掉柯克曼、罗琳甚至我想听到的话
what Kirkman, or Lorraine or even I wanna hear.
‎说出你要说的东西
Say what you need to say.
‎我不知道要说什么
I don't know what that is.
‎问题是 伊莎…
The thing is, Isi...
‎最让我煎熬的是 我想赢
The thing that kills me is that I want it.
‎不只是为了我 还为了这背后的意义
And not just for me, but for what it means.
‎第一位拉丁裔副总统
The first Latino vice president.
‎这是有意义的 但…
That means something. But how...
‎我要怎么表达
how do I express it?
‎说出你的心里话
Speak your truth.
‎说实话
Be honest.
‎我会陪着你 好吗
And I'll be right there, okay?
‎不管如何 我都陪着你
No matter how it goes, I'll be right there for you.
‎我们一起回家 生活还会继续
And we'll go home, and life will go on.
‎晚上好 谢谢你们 ‎给我自我辩白的机会
Good evening, and thank you for giving me the opportunity to explain myself.
‎自我辩白
To explain myself.
‎今晚 我是来道歉的
I came here, tonight, to apologize.
‎但我更需要承担责任
But what I need to do is take responsibility.
‎我16岁时
When I was 16 years of age,
‎带一个无身份的六岁孩子穿过了边境
I took an undocumented six-year-old child across the border.
‎她的父母被杀了 她无处可去
Her parents had been killed, and she had no place to go,
‎但这不是借口
but that's no excuse.
‎我做的事是违法的
What I did was against the law,
‎我要为此担起责任
and I have to take responsibility for that.
‎我要为我做过的事和自己的身份负责
I have to own what I've done and who I am.
‎但首先 我们来看看 ‎马里卢斯圣地亚哥做了什么
But first, let's take a look at what Mariluz Santiago has done.
‎虽然鉴于她进入我们国家的方式
Even though she could never become a citizen,
‎她永远成为不了公民
because of the way she entered our country,
‎但她以优异的成绩从大学毕业
she graduated from college with honors.
‎在美军服役 被派往过阿富汗
She served in the US Army, was deployed in Afghanistan.
‎现在 她是一名教师 回馈社区
Now, she serves her community as a teacher.
‎她成为了让这个国家更强大的一分子
She's become a part of what makes this country great.
‎这不就是移民的故事吗
And isn't that the story of immigration?
‎这也是我的家庭的故事
It's the story of my family, too.
‎我的母亲是德州人
I'm Texan on my mother's side.
‎我父亲是搬到这个国家的移民
My father was an immigrant to this country.
‎他是合法入境
He came here legally.
‎但他还是时常面临
Still, he was constantly threatened with deportation
‎来自他工作的油田雇主的驱逐威胁
by his employers in the oil fields.
‎他被叫作湿背劳工 ‎西班牙佬、棕色男孩
He was called a wetback, a spic, a brown boy.
‎但他的名字叫阿图洛里维拉
But his name was Arturo Rivera.
‎我不想这样
You see, I wanted more than all of that.
‎所以我尽可能同化
So I did my best to assimilate.
‎我改了名字
I changed my name,
‎抛弃我父亲给我的名字 亚伦里维拉
leaving behind Aaron Rivera, my father's name,
‎改成亚伦萧
for Aaron Shore.
‎但今天 我再也不能眼看着 ‎科尼利厄斯莫斯这样的人
But today, I can no longer sit idly by while people like Cornelius Moss
‎利用像马里卢斯圣地亚哥 ‎和我父亲这样的人
use individuals like Mariluz Santiago and my father as boogeymen
‎来让我们与彼此敌对
to turn us against one another.
‎母亲为自己的孩子 ‎寻求更好的生活并不是犯罪
It shouldn't be a crime for a mother to seek a better life for her child.
‎他们的存在不是犯罪
Their existence is not a crime.
‎他们来到这里 做无人关注的工作 ‎那些他们一直在做的苦工
They come here to do the unseen work, the hard work they've always done,
‎不求赞扬 只求奉献
not looking for credit, only looking to contribute.
‎今天早些时候 ‎我提出辞去候选人身份
Earlier today, I offered to resign from the ticket.
‎但柯克曼总统没有接受我的辞职
But rather than accepting my resignation,
‎而是让我向大家讲话
President Kirkman asked me to speak to you.
‎我相信我下面要说的话 ‎代表我们俩共同的心声
And I believe I speak for the both of us when I say,
‎这个国家需要的领导者应该尊重差异
the leadership that this country needs is one that respects differences,
‎而不是将差异妖魔化
not one that demonizes them.
‎所以我很骄傲 ‎能做汤姆柯克曼的竞选伙伴
That's why I'm proud to be Tom Kirkman's running mate.
‎所以我是个骄傲的墨西哥裔美国人…
That's why I'm a proud Mexican-American...
‎骄傲的拉丁裔 骄傲的里维拉
a proud Latino and a proud Rivera.
‎在政治演讲结尾
It's become clich茅 to end political speeches
‎说“天佑美利坚”已是陈词滥调
by saying, "God bless America."
‎但对我来说并非如此
But it's not a clich茅 to me.
‎我认为这是一种祈祷
To me, it is a prayer.
‎愿天佑美利坚
So, may God bless America.
‎感谢各位的聆听
Thank you for listening.
‎-我们可以走了吗我要喝一杯 ‎-当然
-Can we get out of here? Need a drink. -Of course.
‎他讲得很棒 你得承认
He knocked it out of the park, you gotta admit.
‎是的
Yes, he did.
退选                继续参选
‎-该做选择了 ‎-她写得怎样
-Time to pick. -How'd she do on those?
‎她写得很好
Oh, she did great.
‎至于辞职信 那时我在气头上
About the resignation letter, I was angry.
‎你有生气的权利
You had every right to be.
‎你知道该撕哪一封
You know which one to rip up.
‎不 不是那封 另一封
No, not that one, the other one.
‎你真该把这一招演给别人看
Oh, wow. You really ought to take that show on the road.
‎将军
General.
‎总统先生 ‎有新消息要向您汇报 先生
Mr. President, I have an update for you, sir.
‎没事 将军 请讲
It's all right, General. Proceed.
‎刚得到消息 俄罗斯人 ‎在太平洋上击落了他们的图-95
Just got word. The Russians shot down their Tu-95 over the open Pacific.
‎为什么这样做
Why would they do that?
‎我只能推测 但应该是
Well, I can only speculate, but I would imagine
‎他们想确保我们 ‎无法复原Kh-55和它们的弹头
they wanted to ensure we couldn't recover the Kh-55 and their warheads.
‎特别是如果他们发现 ‎我们用坠机的米格上的航空电子设备
Especially if they figured out we hacked their systems
‎侵入了他们的系统的话
using the avionics from the downed MiG.
‎-好的 将军 非常感谢 ‎-谢谢您 先生
-Okay, General, thank you very much. -Thank you, sir.
‎好 我正在把碎片信息拼凑起来
Okay, I'm just connecting the dots here,
‎你是不是刚刚帮我们 ‎挡住了一场核危机
but did you just quarterback us out of a nuclear crisis?
‎-好吧 我得把这个故事传播出去 ‎-不行
-Okay, I gotta get that story out there. -No.
‎-这件事不能宣传 ‎-为什么
-We're not advertising this. -Why not?
‎我们让那架飞机调头的技术是机密
The technology we used to turn the plane around is classified.
‎如果宣传这个意外 那技术也会暴露
We advertise the incident, we advertise that, too.
‎那又怎样将军刚刚暗示 ‎俄罗斯人已经知道了
So what? The general just implied the Russians already know.
‎保持安静是为了俄罗斯人的利益
It's in the Russians' interest to keep it quiet.
‎我们还有其他敌人
We've got other enemies out there.
‎这里就有其他敌人 汤姆 ‎听着 这是天上掉馅饼的好故事
We've got other enemies right here, Tom. Look, a story has fallen into our laps.
‎讲的是你做总统的最艰难的一天
A story about the most difficult day of your presidency.
‎为什么不利用
Why not use that?
‎又来了 “利用”
And there it is. "Use it."
‎“利用这 利用那” ‎一切对你来说都是交易
"Use this. Use that." Everything's transactional with you,
‎沉浸在小小的政治可用度的单元里
wrapped up in tiny little units of political utility.
‎这就是政治
That is politics!
‎我还以为你开始明白了
I was beginning to think that you were beginning to get it.
‎我觉得你可能没有赢得竞选的能力
You know, it occurs to me that you may not have what it takes to win.
‎因为通常赢得竞选的关键就是无情
Because what it takes, more often than not, is ruthlessness.
‎你知道谁有这个品质吗莫斯
And you know who has that? Moss has that.
‎莫斯冰凉黑暗的心充满了无情的品质
Moss has it pumping through his cold, dark heart.
‎真希望能帮你输入一点
I wish I could give you a transfusion.
‎好让你准备好面对现在这些战斗…
Maybe you'd be ready for the knife fight that you're in--
‎好了够了
Okay! Enough!
‎到此为止吧 罗琳
That'll be all, Lorraine.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎这份工作我做了35年
I've kept this job for 35 years.
‎付出的时间比照顾孩子的时间还长
I've given more time to it than I gave to my children.
‎“认识自己是一切智慧的起源”
"Knowing thyself is the beginning of all wisdom."
‎直到现在 ‎我的行政部门都意图保持沉默
Up to now, my civil service has meant silence.
‎在莫斯和 ‎里奇蒙德执政期间 包括现在
During the Moss administration, during Richmond's, even this one.
‎但我在倾听
But I do listen.
‎弗莱格坎德的类鸦片药物 ‎是在莫斯执政期间审批的
FlagKind's opioid was up for approval during Moss' presidency.
‎德特维尔先生时任局长 ‎当时里克特先生
Mr. Detwiler was commissioner, and Mr. Richter, at the time,
‎是我们药品评估与研究中心的负责人
was our head of the Center for Drug Evaluation and Research.
‎内部研究显示 ‎该药有较高的滥用风险
Internal studies suggested the drug had a high potential for abuse.
‎你有证据吗
Do you have proof?
‎都在这
It's all there.
‎德特维尔先生向里克特许诺
Mr. Detwiler guaranteed Mr. Richter a promotion
‎如果他睁只眼闭只眼 ‎盖章通过 就给他晋升
if he turned a blind eye and rubberstamped the approval.
‎几年后 德特维尔先生离开并加入了 ‎弗莱格坎德的董事会
A couple years later, Mr. Detwiler left to join the board of FlagKind.
‎里克特先生成为了局长
Mr. Richter became the commissioner.
‎这是勾结腐败 非常清楚
This is collusion, plain and simple.
‎为什么现在说出来
Why share this now?
‎我在西弗吉尼亚的威廉姆森长大
I grew up in Williamson, West Virginia.
‎那里悠闲平静
It's slow, and it's quiet,
‎人们哪里痛的话 ‎或是在感觉迟钝的时候
and when people feel pain, or they feel a dullness,
‎都会去用处方止痛药
they turn to prescription painkillers.
‎-你听说过滥开处方药吗 ‎-听过
-You've heard of pill mills? -Yeah.
‎在过去十年
Over the last decade,
‎一个人口小于三千的小镇 ‎用掉了两千万粒药
more than 20 million pills for a town of less than 3,000.
‎哪个脑筋正常的医生…
What doctor in his right mind...
‎我认识的很多人已经去世了
Too many people I know have died.
‎拿去 做点什么吧
Take this and do something about it.
公馆
‎这堪比葛底斯堡演说 ‎和肯尼迪的就职演说
That was "four-score," and "ask-not-what-your-country-can-do,"
‎和奥巴马的“我们可以”不分伯仲
"yes-we-can" level oration!
‎我不太想庆祝 仅此而已
I just don't feel like celebrating, that's all.
‎我知道这段时间你不好受 ‎但你的演讲…
I know this has been really hard, but that speech--
‎那不是演讲
It wasn't a speech.
‎是作秀
It was a pony show.
‎不 你在那里 ‎说出了自己的真实想法 很棒
No, you spoke your truth up there, and it was beautiful.
‎人们对此有共鸣 别这么沮丧
People respond to that. Don't shit all over it.
‎我已经不知道什么是真的了 伊莎
I don't know what's true anymore, Isi.
‎我不知道哪些是表演 哪些是真实
I don't know what's for show or what's real.
‎但我知道 好吗我今晚看到了
Well, I do, okay? And I saw it tonight.
‎所有这些人 罗琳、媒体
Look, all these people, Lorraine, the media,
‎他们看到你 只想着如何利用
they look at you and they just see how they can use you.
‎但我看到的是你这个人
But I see you.
‎我在你身上也看到了我的一部分
I see a piece of myself in you.
‎我太为你骄傲了
I'm so fucking proud of you.
‎-我很爱你 ‎-天啊 我真是个大混蛋
-I love you so much. -Jesus. I'm such a fucking asshole.
‎你给自己的压力太大了
You're putting too much pressure on yourself.
‎我和艾米丽上床了
I slept with Emily.
‎那是个错误 我为此非常讨厌自己
It was a mistake, and I hate myself for doing it.
‎相信我 我讨厌自己
Believe me, I hate myself.
‎但我也要为这件事负责
But I have to take responsibility for this, as well.
‎你让我要诚实 所以我就说了
You asked me to be honest, so I'm gonna be honest.
‎我只是希望你能接受…
I just hope you can accept--
‎麦基 我是马斯哈珀 ‎我有独家新闻给你
Maggie. Mars Harper. I got a scoop for you.
‎是关于食品药品管理局与 ‎唯利是图的制药公司相互勾结的故事
Little story about FDA complicity with predatory drug companies.
‎莫斯还在给你少得可怜的报酬
Is Moss still nickel-and-diming you? Mmm, it's more nickels than dimes these days.
‎最近金额越来越少了
-Oh? -By some accounts,
‎算下来 战争基金已经快空了
the war chest is running on empty.
‎我猜你还愿意
Hmm. So I assume you're still open
‎做点小小的兼职
to a little something-something on the side?
‎你的猜想是正确的 ‎怎么你想做什么
You assume correctly. Why? What do you have in mind?
‎飞马座
Pegasus.
‎以色列恶意间谍软件 ‎你比我想的还要邪恶
Malicious Israeli spyware. You're nastier than I thought.
‎你能搞到吗
Can you get it?
‎当然可以 我认识个人
Of course I can. I know a guy.
‎装到莫斯的手机上困难吗
How easy would it be to install it on, say, Moss' cell phone?
‎只要价钱合理 什么事都好办
For the right price, I can make anything easy.
速度和服务
‎这就是朝圣者的方式
‎-有空吗 ‎-有
-Got a minute? -Yeah.
‎我就想让你知道 我准备好回应了
I just wanted to let you know I'm ready to respond.
‎很好 赛斯会帮你写新闻稿
Good. Seth will help you with the press release.
‎我想做的不止是新闻稿
I wanna do more than a press release.
‎我想贡献自己的力量
I'd like to offer my services
‎作为竞选活动的跨性别权益发言人
as a trans rights spokeswoman for the campaign.
‎如果你有兴趣的话
If you'd be interested, that is.
‎当然 请坐
Of course. Please.
‎你介意告诉我 ‎是什么改变了你的想法吗
Do you mind telling me what changed your mind?
‎自从跨越性别之后 ‎我一直都能不被认成男性
Since I transitioned, I've been able to pass.
‎我秘密地生活着 对我来说很容易
I've lived stealth. It's been easy for me.
‎至少相对更容易 ‎和大部分其他人比的话
Easier, at least, compared to a lot of other people.
‎其他人需要伙伴 他们无法发声
Other people who need allies, who don't have a voice,
‎也许能因我获益
and might benefit from mine.
‎这很好 非常好
This is good. Really good.
‎我们早上再讨论细节
We'll go over the specifics in the morning.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎好好休息一下 汤姆
-Try to get some rest, Tom. -
‎晚安
Good night.
‎喂
Yeah?
‎请等待总统电话接入
Hold for the president, please.
‎-今天很不容易吧 ‎-是的 先生
- Hell of a day, wasn't it? -It was, sir.
‎一场这样的危机 ‎让媒体战显得那么微不足道
A crisis like that makes sparring with the media seem so trivial.
‎我觉得你是对的 ‎看不见的工作才是最重要的
I think you were right. It's the unseen work that matters.
‎总之 我在考虑副总统的职位
Anyway, I was thinking about the vice presidency
‎和它的意义
and what it means.
‎事实上 它最终归结为一个问题
And the truth is, it comes down to one question.
‎如果我出了什么事 ‎无法完成我的职责
If something were to happen to me, if I were unable to fulfill my duties,
‎我愿意让我选中的人 ‎在我缺席期间把控大局吗
would I be happy with the person I chose to take the reins in my absence?
‎在这个情况下 我的回答是
And the answer to that question, in this specific instance,
‎当然 你是个好人 亚伦
is absolutely yes. You're a good man, Aaron.
‎谢谢你 先生
Thank you, sir.
‎明早见
See you bright and early tomorrow.
不准入内
黛安 请查看附件中 ‎你要的信息 谢谢 肯尼斯
‎-喂 女士 ‎-伊莱 汉娜呢
-Yes, ma'am. -Eli, where's Hannah?
‎她不接电话
She's not picking up.
‎她可能关机了
Probably turned her phone off.
‎她回去查看啤酒厂了
She went back to the brewery for a look around.
‎哦 天啊
Oh, God.
‎那里肯定有猫腻
Something's definitely dodgy about it.
‎和我们说话的男人想骗过我们 ‎但我和遗传公司确认过
Man we spoke with tried to shine us on, but I confirmed with Genetical
‎天花片段绝对是寄到那里了
and the smallpox bits absolutely shipped there.
‎我正在发一张 ‎已知南非生物武器专家的照片给你
I'm forwarding you a photo of a known South African bioweapons expert.
‎等她回来给她看 ‎也许是我们要找的幕后首脑
Show it to her when she gets back. Could be our ringleader.
黛安路易斯
当前法医年龄估算
‎不必挣扎 威尔士女士
You needn't struggle, Ms. Wells.
‎这样会少些痛苦
It'll be less painful if you don't.
‎我想你一定很好奇
I'm sure you're very curious, eh?
‎这是VX神经毒剂 ‎很难发现 无法解毒
It's a VX nerve agent. Very hard to find. Impossible to neutralize.
‎很快 它就会麻痹你全身的肌肉
Soon, it will cause paralysis in all the muscles of your body,
‎包括你的膈膜
including your diaphragm, which will inexorably result
‎这会让你死于窒息
in your death by asphyxiation.
‎这真的是非常厉害的一种毒剂
It really is a remarkable little toxin indeed.
‎在007电影中
You know, it's commonplace in the 007 movies
‎反派总是对邦德坦白他的邪恶设想
for the villain to confess his nefarious intentions to Bond.
‎告诉他 他只差一点 ‎就可以阻止阴谋了 诸如此类
That he was so close to thwarting said nefarious intentions, etcetera.
‎但你呢 你只差一点点 威尔士女士
But you, you were so very close, Ms. Wells, eh?
‎我天真地以为 ‎陷害那些崇拜希特勒的丑角
Oh, I was naive to think that framing those Hitlerian buffoons
‎就能让你满足
was enough to satisfy you.
‎我很遗憾 ‎你看不到我们的邪恶计划实现了
I do regret that you won't be able to see our nefarious intentions in action.
‎但是 你要知道 将人引向绝路的
But, you know, it's often a belief in one's own invulnerability
‎往往是因为他自认为不可战胜
that brings about one's own demise.
‎很讽刺 是不是
Ironic, isn't it?
‎再见 邦德先生
Goodbye, Mr. Bond.
♪ Is that all there is? ♪
‎你不该给我打电话
You shouldn't be calling me.
‎我们要加快进度了
We're gonna need to accelerate our timetable.
♪ Let's break out the booze ♪
♪ And have a ball ♪
♪ If that's all ♪
♪ There is ♪
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177
本集中所用到的真人采访画面都由纪录片影人提供
他们的观点没有剧本支持 均为个人观点